bharatbajaar.com 2018-02-21

# Privacy Policy | India's latest shopping point website is Bharat-bazaar.com :designer online quality cheap price product.

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We endeavor to comply with laws of other countries but cannot and do not warrant that we do. We do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on systems and the Website controlled by us, but we are not liable for any unauthorized or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to our control, for example advertisers and websites that have links to our Website. You should take note that the information and privacy practices of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks, may be different from ours. Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

**Your Personal Data**

"Personal Data" means any information about you which is personally identifiable, including, without limitation, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, registration name, password and other information from which you can be identified and which you disclose to us at any time.

**Collection of Your Personal Data**

We collect your Personal Data when:

  1.  You create an on-line account;
  2.  You place an order;
  3.  You make a complaint or enquiry or provide other feedback to us;
  4.  You disclose your Personal Data to us through the Website at any other point.

**Use of Your Personal Data**

We use your Personal Data to:

  1. Process and complete orders you place via the Website;
  2. Process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by you;
  3. Monitor, develop and improve the Website and your experience when using the Website;
  4. Process the registration of your Retailers account and maintain your Retailers account;
  5. Where requested by you, to send you marketing materials about new or existing products and special offers .If at any point you change your mind and no longer wish to receive marketing information from us, you can e-mail us at info@bharatbajaar.com and let us know.

**Cookies**

This site uses cookies. One or more of the cookies we use is essential for parts of this website to operate and has already been set. You may delete and block all cookies from this site, but parts of the site will not work.

**Security**

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorised or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the Site, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer.

**Consent**

By submitting data to us or our agent or using the Site, you consent to our use of your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Copyright**

We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action.

This Privacy Policy can change at any time to include / exclude clauses and Bharatbajaar.com does not bear responsibility for updating Users on the same.
